And what a way to finish for Ekaterina Alexandrova.
亚历山德罗娃精彩收官！
北京时间10月6号下午
中网女单1/8决赛
今年温网冠军诺斯科娃
美网之后5场全胜
但这一次
她的反扑为什么没能奏效？
Drops in. Nicely done. Backhand side from Noskova.
落进界内！诺斯科娃反手得分
诺斯科娃的反手也能打出制胜分
先保发之后
她在对手发球局拿到3次机会
先是40比15 再一次占先
却全被救下
Great hands. Yeah.
手上功夫真好
There's the drop shot and great coverage at the net.
放短后 网前覆盖很到位
诺斯科娃在网前还能抢分
底线却开始承压
亚历山德罗娃的反手打得又深又快
接发也敢直接抢
看首盘的两次关键破发
That's a big backhand from Alexandrova.
亚历山德罗娃这记反手很有威力
So, Alexandrova gets the first break of the opening set.
亚历山德罗娃完成首盘首次破发
Can just react, get that return back in play.
及时反应 把接发球送回场内
Good return again from Alexandrova.
又一次漂亮接发！
And she has a double-break lead.
她已经领先两个破发
Bit of a surprise.
确实有些出人意料
Backhand for Alexandrova to close out the opening set.
这记反手 首盘拿下！
So, two breaks of serve, and she hands Linda Noskova
两次破发 让诺斯科娃
her first set loss in her last six matches.
最近六场比赛首次丢盘
An upset brewing perhaps in round four.
第四轮 冷门正在酝酿
首盘2比6
第二盘 诺斯科娃又先保发
再在对手发球局拿到破发点
这是全场第四次机会 也是最后一次
她依然没能兑现
Oh, wow!
噢 太漂亮了！
打到2比2 诺斯科娃还没有掉队
可随后自己的两个发球局都失守
她连丢最后4局
对手的第二盘8个一发球 全部得分
制胜分 诺斯科娃8记 对手32记
第二盘更是2比19
4次破发机会又全都错过
她始终没能把反扑变成比分
温网冠军暂时停步
亚历山德罗娃首次打进中网八强
下一轮对米拉 安德烈耶娃
诺斯科娃下一站能再起势吗？
最后一分 交给现场
And what a way to finish for Ekaterina Alexandrova.
亚历山德罗娃精彩收官！
A dominant effort against the Wimbledon champion
面对温网冠军 她打得很强势
who hasn't lost since the US Open.
对手从美网之后就没输过
Had a five-match win streak going that is now gone.
此前的五连胜 现在终结了
Ekaterina Alexandrova into the quarterfinals in Beijing for the very first time.
亚历山德罗娃首次中网八强
Two and two over the number five seed.
两个六比二 击败五号种子